http://www.cambridgeshire.gov.uk/council/data-protection-and-foi/information-and-data-sharing/privacy-statement

Skip to main contentShare page to TwitterShare page to FacebookShare page as emailPrint this page
Privacy and data protection
As a County Council we provide a large range of different services, as explained throughout our website, and virtually all of these rely on us collecting and using information about individuals.
Everything we do with that information, from how we collect it to how long we keep it for, has to comply with Data Protection legislation. This has been the case for many years, but you will probably be aware that this legislation has now been updated.
This section of our website provides information on our data protection practices.
It brings together our Privacy notices, which are used to inform you of details such as what information we collect, why we collect it, what we use it for, who we share it with, and what rights you have about the information we hold about you.
We have a main council-wide privacy notice that covers our information use in broad terms and then a developing group of service-specific notices that go into more detail.
These notices can be read alongside the details provided when we collect information from you, such as a statement on a form, a service information leaflet or discussed with you in person by one of our staff members.
An Easy Read version of our privacy notice can be found below.
Easy Read Privacy Policy2.7MB–pdfSize: 2.7MBFile format: pdfData Protection Policy 202030KB–pdfSize: 30KBFile format: pdf We conduct Data Protection Impact Assessments (DPIA) for any new processing of personal data. Assessments relating to NHS datasets and Adult Social Care can be viewed below. DPIA_CRDS_Published279KB–pdfSize: 279KBFile format: pdfDPIA_HES_Published300KB–pdfSize: 300KBFile format: pdfDPIA_Mosaic_Published166KB–pdfSize: 166KBFile format: pdf The Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Pseudonymisation and Anonymisation of Data Policy can be found below. Pseudonymisation and Anonymisation of Data Policy 1.0120KB–pdfWhenever we use information, we always limit this to only the details that are needed and we ensure that it is used safely and securely. We require anyone we share information with, or who uses it on our behalf, to do so too. All staff and councillors recSize: 120KBFile format: pdf
Communications with the Council (including online transactions) may be subject to monitoring and recording only for purposes permitted by the Telecommunications (Lawful Business Practice) (Interception of Communications) Regulations 2000  in order to prevent or detect a crime, or investigate or detect the unauthorised use of the service.
Contact
For information relating to Data Protection contact:
E-mail: data.protection@cambridgeshire.gov.uk
Telephone: 01223 699 137
Post: Business Intelligence - Information and RecordsCambridgeshire County Council OCT1224Shire HallCambridgeCB3 0AP
PreviousPrivacy noticeNextOpen dataYou are inCouncilData Protection And FoiInformation And Data SharingPrivacy statementAdult Safeguarding service privacy noticeArchives service privacy noticeBlue Badge service privacy noticeCambridgeshire Music privacy noticeCambridgeshire Pension Fund privacy noticeChildren's and Safeguarding service privacy noticeConnecting Cambridgeshire privacy noticeCoronavirus (Covid-19) privacy noticeEarly Help privacy noticeCoroner service privacy noticeEducation service privacy noticeEnvironment and Commercial services privacy noticeFostering services privacy noticeLibrary service privacy noticeHighways privacy noticeNational Fraud Initiative privacy noticePrivacy noticePublic health coronavirus (Covid-19) privacy noticePublic Health privacy noticeRecruitment privacy noticeRegistration service privacy noticeYouth Offending service privacy noticeTransport privacy notice© 2020 ResidentsBusinessCouncilApply and renewPayReportJobs and CareersContact usPrivacy statementAccessibility statementCookies on our websiteTerms and DisclaimerHelp using online forms
